OGUNTUASE SAMUEL KAYODE

PERSONALINFORMATION

CONTACT ADDRESS Plot 10 sode Estate, Iyana Adeoyo Oluyole Axis,ibadan

EMAIL ADDRESS kayodeolamilekan91@gmail.com

TELEPHONE +2347036384794

STATE OF ORIGIN Ekiti State

NATIONALITY Nigeria

PROFILE SUMMARY	
PROFILE SUIVINART	

A dexterous product sales expert with expertise who enjoys making aggressive sales Strategies to routinely exceed corporate quotas. Passionate about developing long time customers relationship which promotes organization's value and integrity. A professional whom ability to convert a prospect to a reliable customer is engulfed.

CORE COMPETENCIES_

Proficiency in Microsoft packages (Word, Excel and powerpoint)

- Strong communication and analytical skills
- Speaks English , Yoruba and Pidgin English fluently
- Diplomatic in decision making and policy formation
- Meticulous to details and in dealing with clients to maintain the organisations core values

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATION

2010-2015 Ekiti State University Ado Ekiti (B.A (HONS) English and Literary Studies (Second Class Lower Division)

2002-2008 Adladof High School, Ifaki Ekiti (SSCE)

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION_____

Professional diploma in HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGEMENT Obafemi Awolowo University,lle-ife 2017.

WORK EXPERIENCE_____

2008-2009	Eminent Tutorial College, Akure, Ondo State	Tutor
2015-2016	Bobbyjay Computer Institute, Omolayo Plaza, Ado-Ekiti	Secretary
2016-2017	Emmanuel College Ile-Ife (NYSC)	English Teacher
2017. N	Mutual Benefit Life Assurance ltd, Ado-Ekiti	Marketing Executuve

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS_

Participate in all strategy sessions to identify clients and prospects sales opportunities. Ensure target is met as at when due.

Identify and develope strategies based on company's objective and market trend

HOBBIES_

- Reading
- Sports
- Making researches

REFERENCES_

• CHIEF ADENIJI

Administrative Officer

Ekiti State University, Ado-Ekiti

Tel: 08034991842

Email akinadeniji19@yahoo.com

• DR. MRS. LARA OWOEYE

Department of English and Literary Studies.

Ekiti State University, Ado-Ekiti

Tel: 08032500407

Mrs Rhoda Aluko

Regional head

First city monument bank

Boseanumi@gmail.com